export const data = [
  {
    question: "I've been waiting ____ three hours.",
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: false },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: true },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'I only like to go swimming ____ the summer.',
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: true },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "In Kyiv, it's usually very cold ____ the winter.",
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: true },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Don't look at your mobile phone ____ dinner!",
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: true },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: false },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "I've been learning English ____ five years.",
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: false, id: 1 },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: true, id: 2 },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'He has been working out every day ____ six months now.',
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: false, id: 1 },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: true, id: 2 },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Please don't talk ____ the film.",
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: true, id: 1 },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: false, id: 2 },
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'I took trip to the Carpathian Mountains. It was so beautiful! But, it rained ten times ____ my trip.',
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: true, id: 1 },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: false, id: 2 },
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'If you visit Lviv, make sure you try the amazing chocolate ____ your stay.',
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: true, id: 1 },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: false, id: 2 },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'You should brush your teeth ____ two minutes twice a day.',
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: false, id: 1 },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: true, id: 2 },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'I usually wake up a few times ____ the night.',
    answerOptions: [
      { answer: 'during', isCorrect: true, id: 1 },
      { answer: 'for', isCorrect: false, id: 2 },
    ],
  },
]
